On your left!
小心左边!
Pardon me.
原谅我.
I'm sorry.
抱歉.
I know you.
我认识你.
You do?
你认识我?
Yes, you work at the Sheraton.
是的. 你在Sheraton(酒店)工作.
Yes I do. Are you a guest there?
是, 我是. 你是那里的客人吗?
No...
不是...
Oh, you do business at the hotel.
Oh, 你做生意 在酒店.
Yes, I have meetings there.
是的, 我开会在那里.
I'm Jim Bigelow, C.E.O. Sheraton.
我是Jim Bigelow, Sheraton的总裁
How do you do?
你好
William Olson. Front desk.
William Olson. 前台接待.
I'm sorry. I-I-I didn't know you.
对不起. 我-我-我(之前)不认识你
Well, you don't see me there very often.
Well, 你不常在那里看到我.
I only come in for meetings.
我仅仅来开会.
Do you like those?
你喜欢那些(溜冰鞋)吗?
Oh, yes.
Oh, 是的.
Not me. I always try to walk.
我不(喜欢). 我总是试着步行.
Oh, well I usually walk.
Oh, well 我通常步行.
I live here in the city, so I walk everywhere.
我住在市区, 所以我步行去每个地方.
Except when I skate. Or work,of course.
除了当我滑冰时. 或(当我)工作时, 当然了.
I never stop working.
我从不停止工作.
Today's my day-off.
今天是我的休息日.
Well, enjoy it!
Well, 享受它吧!
My last one was three weeks ago!
我上一个(休息日)是3个礼拜之前!